(Howard:)Oh, boy.
(Sheldon:)Despite what her Bible says,
recent archeological studies indicate
(Sheldon:)that although camels are
referenced in the Old Testament,
(Sheldon:)they didn't exist in the Middle East
until hundreds of years later.
(Howard:)I was gonna say we pick up
a cake or a pie.
(Howard:)But an insult to her faith
is always thoughtful.
(Bernadette:)So, what happens next?
I cant tell you that.
But perhaps the killer dropped
(Raj:)a fun and imaginative clue
somewhere in the apartment.
(Penny:)Ooh, I'm gonna check the fridge,
(Penny:)and see if there are
any clues inside a beer.
(Amy:)Hey, I found something.
It locks like a little man
with a briefcase.
Oh, no. That's Clarence Darrow.
(Leonard:)It's from a game Sheldon made up
called Chutes and Lawyers.
(Leonard:)You slide down a chute
and then work your way back up
(Leonard:)through the appellate system.
(Raj:)Well, unlike that,
my games are much more fun.
(Penny:)Can I ask you something? Why do you
like making us do this stuff?